Mahmoud Elzanklony

Link in:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mahmoudelzanklony-6b751a147/

Phone:

+201152296646, +201005663932

Email:

mahmoud_elzanklony@yahoo.com

Summary

Senior Full Stack web developer with experience about 6 years Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including java script, PHP, MySQL. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- Php, oop, api
- Design pattern
- laravel
- mysql, oracle
- Complex problem solver

- Java script, jquery, bootstrap
- vue , vue cli , vuex
- nuxt, vutify
- UI UX

Experience

Front End Developer at caeera - 01/2015 to 05/2016 Full stack at King Saud University - 07/2016 to 05/2018

- Cooperate with students at graduation proejcts to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences proejcts.
- Give online lectures at front end

Full stack at Saudi Ministry of Defense - 01/2019 to 01/2020

Manufacture of military programs for the country

Full stack at BueFree - 05/2019 to 01/2022

Make crm systems, ecommerce websites, etc

Front End Instructor at NTI - 02/2020 until now

Give online lectures to students

Full stack at Algorithma - 03/2022 until now

Make online websites with my team

Education

Bachelor of Science: **Computer Information Systems** – 2019 with grade v.good (82%) **Faculty University**, Zagazig

Languages

Arabic – Mother Language

English – second language